poperblocker.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Poper Blocker

_[Last modified: August 9, 2018]_

###  **Introduction**

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) governs the data collection practices Big Star Labs LP (“ **Company** ”, “ **us** ”, “ **we** ” and “ **our** ”) uses when you use our **_Poper Blocker_** browser add-on extension (“ **Poper Blocker Product** ”). This Privacy Policy is provided to make important and transparent disclosures on **how** or **why** we collect, **share** and **use** our users’ information. Our users’ privacy is important to us. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy carefully prior to using our Poper Blocker Product and use it to make informed decisions.

By using the Poper Blocker Product, you acknowledge the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is an integrated part of the Company’s End User License Agreement (Link: <https://poperblocker.com/terms/>) (“ **Terms of Use** “) and, to the extent that the processing of personal data is based on consent (see below), is a legally binding agreement between you and the Company. Your continued use of the Poper Blocker Product constitutes your acknowledgement and, where applicable, consent to this Privacy Policy. The definitions herein shall have the same meaning as defined in the Terms of Use. If you object to these terms, please do not access or use the Product.

###  **What Information Do We Collect?**

The information we collect is non-identifiable information which may be made available or gathered via the user’s use of the Poper Blocker Product (“ **Non-Personal Information** “). We are not aware of, and cannot determine the identity of the user from which the Non-Personal Information is collected. Non-Personal Information which is collected includes the user’s aggregated browsing usage information and technical information transmitted by the user’s device.

When you install or use the Poper Blocker Product, we collect from you: the type of device, operating system and browsers you are using; the date and time stamp; browsing usage, including visited URLs, clickstream data or web address accessed; TabID; the browser identifier; and your Internet Protocol address (trimmed and hashed so that it cannot be used to identify you).

We may disclose or share this information with third parties as specified below and solely if applicable.

We do not collect from you or share any individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort be used to identify an individual (“ **Personal Information** “) when you install or use the Product. We do collect your Internet Protocol address, which in some jurisdictions is considered Personal Information, but we trim and hash it so that it cannot be used to identify you. In addition, we might keep Personal Information that was voluntarily provided by you if and when you contact us, such as your name and email address, provided that such information will be used solely to communicate with and support you, and will not be shared with any third parties.

###  **How is the Data Used?**

We collect your information during your access or use of the Poper Blocker website or the Poper Blocker Product as detailed above. We use that information based on our legitimate interests in promoting and improving the Poper Blocker Product and our services, on the necessity of such information for the provision of the Poper Blocker Product and our services where applicable (as described in this Privacy Policy) or, where permitted under applicable law, on the implied consent that you provide by using the Poper Blocker Product, or by requesting support, registering for the Poper Blocker Product, or through your use of the various forums and blogs available within the website.

In practice, in order to provide the Poper Blocker Product we need to scan the webpages you browse. Meaning, we use the data collected from you, as detailed and specified above, and transmit it our servers solely for the purpose of enable the Poper Blocker Product and to know when and where there is a popup to block!

We also use Non-Personal Information, aggregated information or statistics regarding user browsing behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, the Product in the form of aggregated data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports, which do not describe or identify any individual user.

###  **How is the Data Shared?**

We do **not** share any Personal Information collected from you with third parties or any of our partners. We may disclose information you submitted if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary:

(i) to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request;

(ii) to enforce our policies (including our policies and agreements), including investigations of potential violations thereof;

(iii) investigate, detect, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or other wrongdoing, suspected fraud or security issues;

(iv) to establish or exercise our rights to defend against legal claims;

(v) to prevent harm to the rights, property or safety of us, our users, yourself or any third party; or

(vi) for the purpose of collaborating with law enforcement agencies or in case we find it necessary in order to enforce intellectual property or other legal rights.

The Non-Personal Information we collect may be used or shared in any of the above circumstances, as well as

(i) for the purpose of providing and improving our Services; or

(ii) internally within the Company to conduct business and marketing analysis, and enhance your experience; or

(iii) with our partners as part of Company’s aggregated data analysis services. If we combine Personal Information with Non-Personal Information, the combined information will be treated as Personal Information for as long as it remains combined.

We may share your Non-Personal Information with our parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control (collectively “ **Affiliated Companies** “) solely if and when applicable or necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We may share Information, including Personal Information, in the event of a corporate transaction (e.g. sale of a substantial part of our business, merger, consolidation or asset sale). In the event of the above, our Affiliated Companies or acquiring company will assume the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy.

Note that we may also appoint third-party service providers (operating under our instructions), who may need access to your Information in connection with their services on our behalf. Transfers of your Personal Information will be made in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

We will take the steps necessary to ensure that international transfers of personal data (including Personal Information) meet all requirements under applicable data protection laws. When personal data collected within the European Economic Area (“ **EEA** “) is transferred outside the EEA, we will take the steps necessary to ensure that the transfer of such data provides sufficient safeguards, and you may exercise your rights, where applicable, to receive information on such transfer mechanism.

 **Cookies and Third-Party Tools**

When you use the Poper Blocker website ([www.poperblocker.com](http://www.poperblocker.com/)) or our Product, we may use Cookies that enable us to identify you. Please note that a “Cookie” is a small text file found in a browser directory, which a website assigns and stores on your computer while you view a website. It is a standard practice to use Cookies, and they are used for different purposes including allowing you to navigate among pages efficiently, facilitating automatic activation of some features, remembering your preferences, and making the interaction between you and various services such as ours easier and faster. In addition, Cookies are used to help customize your user experience. More information about cookies can be found at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Poper Blocker’s website may use third-party tools (e.g. [www.google.com/analytics/](http://www.google.com/analytics/) or [https://keen.io](https://keen.io/)) or third-party content (e.g. [www.youtube.com](http://www.youtube.com/)). These third parties may use and store their own Cookies on your device, which Cookies may collect information about you, including Personal Information, subject to the privacy practices of these third parties. These third-party Cookies may collect information such as how often users access our website, what pages users visit, and when. For additional information on third party Cookies, please check with the relevant third party.

We use the information we receive from third parties such as Google Analytics based on our legitimate interests in promoting and improving the Poper Blocker Product and our services. Note that we do not combine the information collected through the use of third-party tools with any Personal Information collected from you. You may remove Cookies by following the instructions on your device governing the setting of your preferences. Our Cookies do not enable any access to or inspection of other information on your device. If you wish to be notified of when Cookies are placed on your device, you may set your web browser to provide such notices.

 **Opt out right**

You may opt out of the automatic data collection and sharing process of Non-Personal Information described above by deselecting the checkbox next to the words “Enable Overlay Blocking” in the Options page of Poper Blocker.

After you opt out, we will no longer automatically collect and share your Non-Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. Note that once you opt out, part of the Services provided by Poper Blocker will no longer be available, meaning overlays will not be blocked automatically.

###  **User Rights**

Please note that, unless you instruct us otherwise, we retain the information we collect for as long as needed to provide the services described herein and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. In the event you do not agree to the aforesaid collection, use and share of data, please uninstall or disable the Poper Blocker Product immediately from your device.

Where provided under applicable law (e.g., within the European Union), you may have the right to ask us to delete Personal Information which you have provided to us,  subject to applicable exceptions, such as in order to preserve that information for anticipated litigation or demands from a regulator, or some or all of the following rights: the right to obtain information on our use of your Personal Information, the right to obtain a copy thereof, the right to data portability, the right of data rectification, the right to object to processing based on our legitimate interests, the right to restriction of the processing, and the right to withdraw your consent.

In order to assert any of these rights, please contact our Data Protection Officer at: dpo@poperblocker.com. Note that we may request proof of identity, and we reserve the right to charge a fee where allowed by law, such as in circumstances where your request is excessive.

In addition, you may have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, subject to applicable law (as is the case in the European Union).

###  **How do we safeguard your information?**

We make best efforts to use security methods and encryptions when handling sensitive data (i.e., handle the user data securely, including transmitting it via modern cryptography). Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through the Poper Blocker Products cannot be 100% guaranteed.

###  **Minors**

Children under 13 are **prohibited** from using the Poper Blocker Product. In the event that we become aware that a user under the age of 13 has shared any information, we will discard such information. If you have any reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has shared any information with us, please contact our Data Protection Officer at: dpo@poperblocker.com. If you are under 18, please be sure to read this policy with your parents or legal guardians and ask questions about things you do not understand.

###  **Amendments**

We reserve the right to periodically amend or revise the Privacy Policy; material changes will be effective immediately upon the display of the revised Privacy Policy. The last revision date will be reflected in the “Last modified” heading. Your continued use of the Poper Blocker Product, following the notification of such amendments on our website, constitutes your acknowledgement of such amendments to the Privacy Policy and where the processing of personal data is based on consent (see above) your agreement to be bound by the terms of such amendments.

###  **How to contact us?**

If you have any questions about these terms, please contact us at: [support@poperblocker.com](mailto:support@poperblocker.com)
